[Music]
hi this video explains the importance of
easy onboarding to business Central from
a human aspect it's a clip from a launch
made video for 2023 release Wave 2 but
it's equally relevant today let's turn
it over to Sarah who will tell us more
about it so enough with the business
motivations for investing into
onboarding let's talk about The Human
Side the more emotional side of
onboarding to a new service or to a new
thing so Sarah I wondered can you talk
to us about what does it mean to on
board to something new and how have we
brought that philosophy into business
Central yes I can thank you
son here you see someone entering a
hotel in a new city where he has never
been before so he's a little uncertain
if he's at the right
place but hopefully he will get a warm
and personal welcome and he will feel
expected and comfortable finding his way
around and getting the most out of his
stay trying out a new product for the
first time can be a bit similar you can
be a little uncertain if you're at the
right
place and maybe even a bit overwhelmed
by all the information so having a clear
indication of where to start and being
able to find your way around is really
important for a good first
experience
and what we found in our studies is that
while some users like to go and explore
on their own right away others might
need a little more handholding along the
way so when designing the onboarding
framework for business Central it was
crucial for us to really cater for both
of these two types of users ensuring we
didn't block the path to anyone yet
still making sure that we had relevant
in
context uh guidance along the way to
getting productive with business Central
today you will hear more about how you
as a partner can scale this onboarding
experience to even more
customers while still ensuring relevant
onboarding content to your customers
business needs to learn more visit
aka.ms BC onboarding thank you for
watching
[Music]